Emmanuel
(God with us Matthew 1:23)
My name is Honorable Major
General Patrick Rafel Zamoi.
From the Republic of South Sudan.
The lady besides me is my beautiful wife.
People of God, God has done wonders in our life.
We came here with my wife five years ago in 2012.
The problem that brought us here was marital problem,
I had a stroke due to High blood pressure.
And limitation in progress.
When we came here the men of God located my wife,
and we were blessed with the morning water.
When we went back home,
we ministered the morning water
with my wife together and prayed along.
Immediately the door opened for us
The most important thing for us was
to have an official marriage
the christian way in the church.
In the same year 2012 in November,
we had a wonderful marriage ceremony.
which was very successful and
appreciated by many people.
Secondly, In 2013 the high blood pressure was still there
My muscles were stiff and was admitted in hospital.
The only help was from my wife
ministering the morning water to me.
until we were referred to Nairobi Hospital.
When we reached Nairobi Hospital they
checked every system through CT scan.
All the system was checked and
nothing was found in my body.
The shape of my face which had
changed returned back to normal
The stiffness and the high blood pressure
stopped since that time to date.
{So we've been listening to our father
of how they came to the
Synagogue Church of All Nations facing
marital problems health challenges
and stagnation in their business and career.
And that the doors of God Almighty
the doors of heaven opened
when they came to the Synagogue Church of All Nations
and received the morning water.
So from there sir after you received your
wonderful healing through the morning water.
What started happening in your life after there?}
Now after receiving the healing the breakthrough came.
The first was in 2014 I received a phone call
from the office of the president
the Republic of South Sudan
and I was blessed with a brand new car,
the latest model V8.
Major General Patrick Raphael & Wife
Morning water testimony.
After that I was taking a course in Christian University
During my studies, I ministered the morning water.
When the results came out I had
first class upper division.
Major General Patrick Raphael & Wife
Morning water testimony.
Then after that I received a call,
I was in reserved list from the army
as a Brigadier General.
I received a call that I'm back to the
army to reinstate my job
with the promotion to make a general in the army
Major General Patrick Raphael & Wife
Morning water testimony.
In the same year, August 15th I was
appointed as a caretaker governor
of Western Equatorial States Republic of South Sudan.
Major General Patrick Raphael & Wife
Morning water testimony.
Again in the same year on the 24th of December,
new states were created in the
Republic of South Sudan
from 10 states It was created to 28 states.
I was appointed as the Governor of Goodway States.
Major General Patrick Raphael & Wife
Morning water testimony.
Then from there, while I was
the Governor of Gbudue States,
most of the people know that South Sudan
was having a problem of war.
there was conflict in South Sudan.
I was touring the state, on my way back from
the tour back to the State Headquarters
I was in a huge army convoy escort that
was taking me back to the Headquarters.
I fell into an ambush
The ambush was just very close
to the roadside, but I survived.
More than 10 bullets were fired at my car,
you will see later.
I survived the attack through the ministering of the morning water and the sticker.
Major General Patrick Raphael & Wife
Morning water testimony.
Again, It did not end there after we sign
the compromise peace agreement
It was mentioned that it was good enough
to implement the agreement fully by adding other states
to the previous 28 state that we had.
Other states were created this year January.
I was again blessed to be appointed as
the governor of Tunbridge State
{Come on put your hands together for Jesus
If you know that God Almighty has brought
you here to release the same kind of breakthrough
on your business, on your career on your future,
on your finances put your hands together for Jesus!}
Major General Patrick Raphael & Wife
Morning water testimony.
Well sir, we really thank God for
all the way long Jesus Christ
has seen you through and we want
you to just place more emphasis.
What was the medium that God
Almighty used to bring
about all this breakthrough this
protection and this blessing in your life?}
The medium, God has used to bring me all this blessing
is this morning water.
This morning water has really served
a purpose in my life
and my life has changed clockwise to who I am today.
Being called today a more Honorable member holding
a diplomatic passport moving through out the nation.
Major General Patrick Raphael & Wife
Morning water testimony.
{Sir we can see some documents and
some pictures on the board over there
Will you please take your time and show us one
by one what are these pictures and documents?}
These are some of the few documents and photos
that I have been talking about.
This is the brand-new vehicle which was donated to me
by his Excellence the President of
the Republic of South Sudan.
A 2014 V8 the latest model at that time.
In the second photo is when I was
called back from reserve list,
I was promoted to the rank of Major General
And here is the Chief of Staff
administering the promotion of Major
General upon my shoulder.
Major General Patrick Raphael & Wife
Morning water testimony.
This one here, is the convoy I was talking about
I was in convoy carrying out government
duties that on our way back
we fell into ambush.
This how my car was sprayed with bullets.
As you can see from here, this is another bullet
the one which was aimed directly
at me here did not hit me.
The driver was wounded slightly on his hand.
Many bullets were fired at the engine
and it stopped instantly.
we had to pull the car.
As you can see here in the newspaper,
Our 'Juba Monitor'
it reads "Gbudue Governor
survives assassination attempt"
Here I am in the Newspaper,.
The one up here, is the certificate of excellence.
This certificate is awarded to his
his Excellency Patrick Rafael Zamoi
first class Upper in the university
- my masters program.
Major General Patrick Raphael & Wife
Morning water testimony.
Hallelujah
This documents here is written
to the Republic of South Sudan
from the office of the President,
this is the appointment letter.
This was the first appointment as the territorial
governor for Western Equatorial
State as you can see here.
Again when the 28 states were created
I was appointed as the governor
of Governor of Gbudue State.
It is here.
Again, when 33 states were created I was appointed
as a governor of tembridge state to
which I am now the current governor.
Which is here.
Put your hands together for Jesus Christ!
We have so many but because the board is so small,
we just decide to put these few
document to show what God has done for us.
The blessing that God has given
me through the morning water.
Emmanuel!
(God with us, Matthew 1:23)
My name is Mrs Emmalyne Zamoi from
the Republic of South Sudan.
The Lord has been so wonderful to us through
the medium of this morning water and the sticker.
My husband has already said it all,
I just want to add some few things.
Immediately in 2012 when we returned from here
because we had this problem.
I was also looking for a job because since
I graduated I didn't find anything to do.
After we returned from here less than one year
Immediately I was appointed in the
Commission for Refugees Affair
I serve there as a Monitoring and Evaluation Officer
Through the morning water.
{Hallelujah put your hands together for Jesus!
All the problems we had in our marital life stopped.
We used to quarrel and we experienced
a lot of problems,
we had nowhere to solve our issue but since that time
we were able to resolve all the issues
there was no quarreling
Nothing again. I praise the Lord
{Hallelujah put your hands together for Jesus,
if you know Jesus is going to restore
your peace and your breakthrough today.
Put your hands together!
Madam we know you still have so much to say.
But we want you to use this opportunity
now to give a word of advice to people
watching you all over the world who are
still engaging in fights and arguments
with their husband with their wives
and going through the same
trouble that you and your husband once were.
My advice to the viewers all over the world is that,
whatsoever problem; whatsoever situation
you are going through don't run from God
but run to God take your problems to God.
As today I am an eyewitness of all my problems that
Jesus has carried on his shoulder.
My advice to viewers all of the world
and those who have been doubting the Word of God
Indeed God is real and Jesus never said goodbye.
He is still the same yesterday, today and tomorrow.
This place here is a Holy ground,
I had a lot of problems in my marital
life in and in my life
Since I stepped my foot here
Even people in my own country started wondering,
is this the same Zomorielwee? I change completely.
I stopped drinking too much beer and whiskey.
I stopped chasing after women.
So I became faithful to my wife
as I'm speaking today.
Major General Patrick Raphael & Wife
Morning water testimony.
So, please my brothers, those who are married like me,
I know you are going through the same
problem I went through.
The solution for your problem is to
come to this arena of Liberty.
your problem will be solved and you'll be flying
with wings just like me.
Please you're welcome here.
{Amen! a wonderful word of advice to all and sundry
that they should seek Jesus Christ in any living
church of which the Synagogue Church
Of All Nations is one of them.
And Jesus will meet them at the point of their needs.
Lastly sir please tell us about this morning water
give the world a word of advice about this.}
This morning you are looking at is not an ordinary water.
The miracle it has done you
have seen it in my life.
And it is going to be the same for you.
I Invite all of you who have still not
come here to please find a way.
How you can reach here and find one for yourself
and be free from the devil like
how I have been free today.
But you'll not be free finally the attack will be there.
When the attacks come it does
not mean you are not a real Christian.
It is again to strengthen your faith so that you continue
to pray more to Jesus Christ who will
heal you and help you.
{Amen!
Sir we thank God Almighty
For what God Almighty has done in your life and
this wonderful testimony you've given today.
We want to encourage you, you are blessed, and you are delivered by the word of God.
so continue to make God's Word
the standard for your life,
and better is not good enough the best is yet to
come for you and your family in Jesus name.}
Amen
TT Lizz ndungu
Date 31/10/2018